Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: National Security, 1976-1997; (60 boxes)
  - North, Oliver L., 1990s (Folder 2, Box 198)
  - North Korea, 1987-1988 (Folder 3, Box 198)
    North Korea
  - Nuclear freeze, 1981-1983 (Folder 4, Box 198)
    Cold War, Defense
  - Nuclear freeze, 1981-1983 (Folder 5, Box 198)
  - NWLF-BARC, 1976-1977 (Folder 6, Box 198)
    New World Liberation Front, Bay Area Research Collective
  - NY State Police-[William F.] Haddad report, 1977 (Folder 7, Box 198)
    New York, Police
  - NY World Trade Center bomb, 1993 (Folder 8, Box 198)
    Bombing, New York, Terrorism
  - Occi [Occidental Petroleum Corporation], 1980s (Folder 9, Box 198)
    Oil Security
  - Occidental Petroleum Corp. Correspondence, 1991 (Folder 10, Box 198)
  - Office of Strategic Services, 1977-1981 (Folder 1, Box 199)
    CIA, Espionage, OSS, Veteran Spies
  - Ollman, Bertell - Beall - Millar (Folder 2, Box 199)
    Education
  - [Omissions in The New Deal Lawyers], 1982 (Folder 3, Box 199)
    Irons, Peter H.
  - On Company Business, 1980-1982 (Folder 4, Box 199)
    CIA, PBS Documentary
  - 073-PanAm-Karachi, 1986 (Folder 5, Box 199)
    Hijacking, Palestinians, Pan American Flight 073
  - Ott, Bruce D.: Horton, Brian P.: Mira, Francisco, 1982-1985 (Folder 6, Box 199)
  - Ozal/[Hosni] Mubarak [assassination attempt], 1988-1995 (Folder 7, Box 199)
    Assassination, Mubarak, Hosni
  - Paisley, John A., 1978-1980 (Folder 8, Box 199)
    Investigation on Death, Newspaper Clippings
  - Palme, Olaf, 1986-1989 (Folder 9, Box 199)
    Palme, Olaf
  - Pan Am Flight 103, 1988-1989 (Folder 10, Box 199)
    Airplane Bombing, Lockerbie, Scotland
  - Panama, 1989-1990 (Folder 11, Box 199)
    Bush, Covert Actions, Noriega, Panama
  - Panama, 1989-1990 (Folder 12, Box 199)
  - Part 1 Active Measures, Quiet War: Part 2 Two Socialist Revolutions, ca. 1980s (Folder 13, Box 199)
    Socialism
  - PBS-CPB-NPR, 1978-1980 (Folder 14, Box 199)
    Investigation, Media
  - P.D. and domestic intelligence: (Test-Senate Subcommittee on Criminal Law and Procedures), 1977 (Folder 15, Box 199)
    Intelligence, Police Department
  - P.D. intelligence cuts, 1970s (Folder 16, Box 199)
  - Philadelphia, 1977-1981 (Folder 17, Box 199)
    MOVE, Police Department
  - Pearl Harbor (50th anniversary), 1991 (Folder 18, Box 199)
  - Pelton, Ronald W., 1986 (Folder 1, Box 200)
    Espionage, Trial
  - PFIAB report-dist, comment, 1981 (Folder 2, Box 200)
  - PFIAB II, 1981-1985 (Folder 3, Box 200)
  - Philippines, 1980-1983 (Folder 4, Box 200)
    Manilla, Newspaper Clippings, Philippines
  - David Atlee Phillips, July 7, 1988 (Folder 5, Box 200)
    Funeral Service Pamphlet
  - Pike [Otis] Committee, 1976 (Folder 6, Box 200)
    CIA, Kissinger, Obstruction of Justice
  - Pitts, Earl E., 1996-1997 (Folder 7, Box 200)
  - PLP-Progressive Labor Party, 1978-1979 (Folder 8, Box 200)
    Progressive Labor Party
  - Pollack, Sandy, 1980s (Folder 9, Box 200)
    Plane Crash, United States Peace Council
  - Pollard, Jonathan J., 1985-1994 (Folder 10, Box 200)
    Espionage, Foreign Intelligence
  - Pollard, Jonathan J., 1985-1994 (Folder 11, Box 200)
    U.S. Ambassador, Espionage
  - Polygraphs, 1976-1993 (Folder 12, Box 200)
    Federal Agencies, Polygraph Use
  - Pope John Paul II [assassination attempt], 1984-1985 (Folder 13, Box 200)
  - Pope John Paul II [assassination attempt], 1983-1985 (Folder 14, Box 200)
  - "Kathy" Power, 1993-1994 (Folder 1, Box 201)
    Anti-War, Trials, Vietnam
  - Press packet, 1978-1982 (Folder 2, Box 201)
    Agee, CIA, Covert Action, El Salvador, Nicaragua
  - Prime, Geoffrey A., 1982 (Folder 3, Box 201)
    Britain, Espionage, Soviet Union
  - Private counsel (government rep and fees), 1977-1982 (Folder 4, Box 201)
    Federal Lawyers, Justice Department, Legal Fees
  - Private intelligence files, 1978-1993 (Folder 5, Box 201)
    Domestic Intelligence, Espionage, Private Eye
  - "Progressive"-H. bomb, 1978-1979 (Folder 6, Box 201)
    "The Progressive", Publication of article on hydrogen bomb construction
  - Protection bills, 1977-1979 (Folder 7, Box 201)
    Amendments to the National Security Act
  - Publication Listings - Print and Music, 1992-1993 (Folder 8, Box 201)
    Out-of-Print Espionage Books
  - Rahman, Sheik Omar [Abdel], 1993 (Folder 9, Box 201)
    Bombing, Egypt, World Trade Center
  - RCMP, 11977-1982 (Folder 10, Box 201)
    Royal Canadian Mounted Police
  - RCP-Rev. C-P ([Bob] Avakian), 1979-1985 (Folder 11, Box 201)
    Ku Klux Klan, Mao Tse Tung, Revolutionary Communist Party, Riots
  - RCP [Revolutionary Communist Party], 1980-1992 (Folder 12, Box 201)
    La Ciencia de la Revolucion, Revolutionary Communist Party
  - Reagan, Ronald executive order, 1981 (Folder 13, Box 201)
    Counterintelligence, Intelligence, Standards of Conduct
  - Reagan, Ronald - transition, 1980-1981 (Folder 1, Box 202)
    Presidential Appointments, Reagan, Transition Team
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1980-1992 (Folder 2, Box 202)
    Brezhnev, Communism, Detente, Soviet Union
  - Reagan [Ronald] assassination attempt, 1981-1989 (Folder 3, Box 202)
    Assassination, Hinckley
  - Reagan [Ronald] package, 1984 (Folder 4, Box 202)
    Anti-Terrorism
  - "Reciproity" (Foreign Missions Act), 1983-1985 (Folder 5, Box 202)
    Diplomats, Espionage, Foreign Missions Act
  - Red guerrilla resistance, ca. 1984 (Folder 6, Box 202)
    Notes, RGR
  - Rees-HISC project, 1980s (Folder 7, Box 202)
  - Religious leaders in El Salvador, 1981-1982 (Folder 8, Box 202)
    Central America, El Salvador, Pope
  - Reporters Committee v. AT and T, 1979 (Folder 9, Box 202)
    American Telephone and Telegraph Company, Freedom of the Press
  - Restrictions-imposed and self, 1980-1986 (Folder 10, Box 202)
    CIA, FBI, Intelligence Restrictions
  - Riot Miami, 1980 (Folder 11, Box 202)
    Miami, Racism, Riots
  - Rome-Vienna-airports, 1986 (Folder 12, Box 202)
    Airport security, Terrorism
  - Rowan, Carl, 1982-1988 (Folder 1, Box 203)
    Gun Control, Newspaper Clippings, Shooting
  - Rushdie, Salman, 1989 (Folder 2, Box 203)
    Iran, Protests, "Satanic Verses"
  - Sabotage, 1986-1989 (Folder 3, Box 203)
    California, Wildfires, Yellowstone
  - Sadat [Anwar] [assassination], 1981-1990 (Folder 4, Box 203)
    Assassinations, Sadat,
  - SALDAC, 1977-1980 (Folder 5, Box 203)
    Special Agents Legal Defense Committee
  - Sanctuary, 1985-1989 (Folder 6, Box 203)
    Deportations, FBI
  - Scientology, 1983-1986 (Folder 7, Box 203)
    "Battlefield Earth", Newspaper Clippings
  - Scranage [Sharon]-[Michael A.] Soussoudis, 1985 (Folder 8, Box 203)
    CIA, Espionage, Ghana
  - Seberg, Jean, 1979-1981 (Folder 9, Box 203)
    Biography, Black Panther Party, FBI, Gary
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation correspondence, 1988 (Folder 10, Box 203)
    Intelligence Oversight Act 1988
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - El Salvador Defectors, 1980s (Folder 11, Box 203)
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Newsletter "Nightwatch", October, November 1986 (Folder 12, Box 203)
    Arms Control, FBI, KGB, National Security
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Newsletter "Nightwatch", March, April, June, July, August, September, November, December 1987 (Folder 13, Box 203)
    Disinformation, National Security, Soviet Union
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Newsletter "Nightwatch", January, February, April, May, July, October, November 1988 (Folder 14, Box 203)
    Arms Control, Soviet Union, Strategic Defense Initiative
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Newsletter "Nightwatch", January, February, March 1989 (Folder 15, Box 203)
    Disarmament, KGB, Gorbachev
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation "Nightwatch" Special Report: "International Narcotics Trafficking: The Soviet Connection", May 1987 (Folder 1, Box 204)
    Drugs, Soviet Union
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Situation Report, March 1978 (Folder 2, Box 204)
    CIA, FBI, Intelligence, Soviet Union, Terrorism
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Congressional Counterintelligence Awareness Course, ca. 1980s (Folder 3, Box 204)
    Counterintelligence
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation 1988 National Intelligence Issues Survey (Folder 4, Box 204)
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Reprint Series - "The Trust", July 1989 (Folder 5, Box 204)
    Dzerzhinsky, Felix
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Reprint Series, "Soviet Active Measures in the United States 1986-1987", 1988 (Folder 6, Box 204)
    Arms Control, Soviet Intelligence
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation Reprint "Soviet Influence Activities: A Report on Active Measures and Propaganda: 1986-1987", January 1988 (Folder 7, Box 204)
    Propaganda, Soviet Intelligence
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - telephone memos, 1988-1989 (Folder 8, Box 204)
    Telephone Conference Report, Transmittal
  - Security and Intelligence and Foundation Notes, 1987-1989 (Folder 9, Box 204)
    McNamara, Memos, Notes
  - Security and Intelligence Fund and Foundation - Letters, 1979-1989 (Folder 10, Box 204)
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - "Firing Line", July 8, 1987 (Folder 11, Box 204)
    "Sovietology"
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Various newspaper and magazine articles, 1980s (Folder 12, Box 204)
    Disinformation, Intelligence
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Immigration exclusion and deportation amendments of 1987 (Folder 13, Box 204)
    Immigration and Nationality Act
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Agenda of the meeting of the board of directors, 1987 (Folder 14, Box 204)
    Personnel
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation/Fund - membership information, 1982 (Folder 15, Box 204)
    Membership Card and Form, McNamara
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1987-1988 (Folder 16, Box 204)
    Administration, Employment, Security
  - Security and Intelligence Foundation - folder, ca. 1980s (Folder 17, Box 204)
    President's Report
  - Senate Intelligence Committee, 1976-1984 (Folder 18, Box 204)
    Congressional Record, Newspaper Clippings
  - Senate Intelligence Committee, 1976-1984 (Folder 19, Box 204)
    CIA, FBI, Intelligence, Senator Biden
  - Senate-Left, 1977-1982 (Folder 1, Box 205)
    CIA, FBI, Newspaper Clippings, Senator Ted Kennedy
  - Senate Passes Bill Requiring 48-Hour Covert Action Notice, ca. 1980s (Folder 2, Box 205)
    Iran-Contra
  - Senate Subcommittee on Security and Terrorism, 1981-1986 (Folder 3, Box 205)
    CIA, Communism, Congressional Record, Intelligence, Terrorism
  - Sessions, William S., 1987-1993 (Folder 4, Box 205)
    FBI, Waco
  - Shadrin [Nicholas George]-[Nikolai F.] Artamonov, 1977-1981 (Folder 5, Box 205)
    Espionage, Missing Spy
  - Anti-Shah demonstrations, 1977-1979 (Folder 6, Box 205)
    Iran-Contra, Islamic Revolution
  - S. 1612 (7/79) Hatch Revision, 1979 (Folder 7, Box 205)
    FBI Charter, Hatch
  - Shevchenko [Arkady] and UN, 1978-1985 (Folder 8, Box 205)
    Diplomats, Espionage, Soviet Defectors, United Nations
  - SIC II, 1982-1989 (Folder 9, Box 205)
    CIA, FBI, Reagan, Senate Intelligence Committee
  - SIC-CISPES, 1980-1988 (Folder 1, Box 206)
    Senate Intelligence Committee, FBI, Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador
  - SLA, 1976-1977 (Folder 2, Box 206)
    Kidnapping, Symbionese Liberation Army, Trial
  - Smith, Richard Craig, 1984-1986 (Folder 3, Box 206)
    Counterintelligence, Espionage, FBI, Trial
  - Smith, William French (Attorney General), 1982-1984 (Folder 4, Box 206)
    Obituary, Speeches
  - Snepp, Frank; Stockwell; Jordan; McGehee; Eveland, 1977-1980 (Folder 5, Box 206)
    CIA, Censorship, "Decent Interval", Trial
  - Sonnenfeldt, Helmut, 1976 (Folder 6, Box 206)
    Eastern Europe, Soviet Union, United States Foreign Policy
  - Sorensen [Theodore], 1976-1977 (Folder 7, Box 206)
    Carter, CIA, Presidential Appointments
  - Sorensen [Theodore], 1976-1977 (Folder 8, Box 206)
  - South African Communists, 1981 + 1991 (Folder 9, Box 206)
    Communism, Marxism, South Africa, Terrorism
  - "Soviet Support for International Terrorism", 1981 (Folder 10, Box 206)
    Foundation for Democratic Education, Soviet Union, Terrorism
  - Soviet active measures notes, 1982 (Folder 11, Box 206)
    KGB, McNamara, Notes, Soviet Union
  - Soviet submarine-Sweden, 1981-1985 (Folder 12, Box 206)
    USSR, Military, Newspaper Clippings, Sweden
  - Space shuttle leak, 1984-1985 (Folder 13, Box 206)
    Information Security, Space Shuttle, The Washington Post
  - Special tasks (Pavel Sudoplatov), 1994 (Folder 14, Box 206)
    Atomic Weapons, Espionage, KGB, Sudoplatov
  - Spetsnaz [Soviet military intelligence], 1985-1988 (Folder 15, Box 206)
    Intelligence, Soviet Union
  - 2nd Amendment, 1990-1993 (Folder 16, Box 206)
    Gun Control
  - "Spy Dust" [tracking chemical], 1985-1986 (Folder 17, Box 206)
    Chemicals, Espionage, Moscow, Soviet Union, United States Embassy
  - Spycatcher (autobiography of Peter Wright), 1986-1995 (Folder 18, Box 206)
    Censorship, Espionage, MI5
  - SSST-testimony CSC-OPM records, 1981 (Folder 19, Box 206)
    Hale Foundation, McNamara, Senate Subcommittee on Security and Terrorism
  - Statement of the Hon. John M. Maury., July 21, 1981 (Folder 20, Box 206)
    Association of Former Intelligence Officers, Intelligence Reform Act of 1981
  - State Prosecution-Brinks, 1983 (Folder 1, Box 207)
    Radicals, Robbery, Terrorism
  - "Stealth" leak, 1980-1981 (Folder 2, Box 207)
    B2 Bomber, Stealth Bomber, Spirit, F-117 Nighthawk
  - Sterling, Claire, 1980-1981 (Folder 3, Box 207)
    "The Terror Network: The Secret War of International Terrorism"
  - Sting, 1976 (Folder 4, Box 207)
    Newspaper Clippings, Police Entrapment, Trial
  - Straight, Michael, 1983 (Folder 5, Box 207)
    Britain, Espionage, Scandal
  - Stockwell, John (author), 1977-1978 (Folder 6, Box 207)
    CIA, Snepp, "The Secret War"
  - Law Suits (general), 1978-1982 (Folder 7, Box 207)
    Federal Lawsuits, Justice Department
  - Suit immunity, 1979-1985 (Folder 8, Box 207)
    FBI, Halperin, Kissinger
  - Suits (impact, No.s, etc.), 1977-1982 (Folder 9, Box 207)
    FBI, Kelley, Lawsuits
  - Surreptitious-BBJ's legality, 1976-1981 (Folder 10, Box 207)
    Black Bag Jobs, Break-Ins, CIA, FBI, Surreptitious Entries
  - SWP [Socialist Workers Party], 1981-1982 (Folder 11, Box 207)
    Brown vs. Socialist Workers Party, Sedition, Supreme Court Cases
  - SWP-Socialist Workers Party: decision-comments, notes, 1976-1981 (Folder 12, Box 207)
    Congressional Records, Councils Against Communist Aggression, FBI
  - Tabatabai [Ali Akbar], Assassin, 1980-1981 (Folder 13, Box 207)
    Assassination, FBI, Iran, Protests
  - TACA bomb threat, 1984 (Folder 1, Box 208)
    Transportes Aereos del Continente Americano
  - Terror-[US] Capitol bombing, 1989-1990 (Folder 2, Box 208)
  - Terror-CIA, 1976-1982 (Folder 3, Box 208)
    Terrorism, Central Intelligence Agency
  - Terror-El Salvador: FMLN assassinations, 1989-1991 (Folder 4, Box 208)
    El Salvador, Terrorism
  - Terror-FBI annual analysis, 1982-1987 (Folder 5, Box 208)
    FBI, Reports, Terrorism
  - Terror-FBI annual analysis, 1982-1987 (Folder 6, Box 208)
  - Terror-FBI annual analysis, 1982-1987 (Folder 7, Box 208)
  - Terror groups, 1995 (Folder 8, Box 208)
  - Terror groups, 1995 (Folder 9, Box 208)
  - Terror groups, 1995 (Folder 1, Box 209)
    Bombing, Oklahoma City, McVeigh, Nichols, Terrorism
  - Terrorism, 1981-1993 (Folder 2, Box 209)
    Islamic Extremists, Radicals, Terrorism, WACO
  - Terrorism, 1981-1993 (Folder 3, Box 209)
    Bombing, Hijacking, Islamic Extremists, World Trade Center
  - Terrorism, 1982-1992 (Folder 4, Box 209)
    FBI, Iran, Media, PLO, Qaddafi, Terrorism
  - Terpil [Frank]-[Edwin Paul] Wilson-[Kevin] Mulcahy, 1980-1985 (Folder 5, Box 209)
    Arms Trafficking, CIA, "Merchants of Death", Terrorism,
  - The Washington Report, 1976-1982 (Folder 6, Box 209)
    Africa, Arms Control, Castro, National Security, Persian Gulf, SALT II, Vietnam
  - Third World, 1979 (Folder 7, Box 209)
    Castro, Cuba, Tito
  - Thornburgh, Richard L., 1988-1989 (Folder 8, Box 209)
    Attorney General, Bush
  - Tort bills and states, 1977-1979 (Folder 9, Box 209)
    Congressional Record, HR 2659, HR 9437, S 2117
  - Transcripts, 1976-1979 (Folder 1, Box 210)
    "60 Minutes", CBS, CIA Roundtable, "Face the Nation"
  - Transcripts, 1978-1979 (Folder 2, Box 210)
    NBC, "Spying for Uncle Sam"
  - Treholt, Arne, 1985-1986 (Folder 3, Box 210)
    Espionage, Norway, Soviet Union
  - Hanafi trial, 1977-1981 (Folder 4, Box 210)
    Hanafi, Muslims
  - Turner, Stansfield, 1977-1985 (Folder 5, Box 210)
    CIA, Intelligence Community, Presidential Appointments
  - Turner, Stansfield, 1977-1985 (Folder 6, Box 210)
    CIA, "Face the Nation" Transcript, Speeches
  - TWA Flight no. 847, 1985 (Folder 7, Box 210)
    Hijacking, Terrorism
  - TWA Flight no. 847, 1985 (Folder 8, Box 210)
  - TWA Flight no. 847, 1985 (Folder 1, Box 211)
  - UFF-United Freedom Front: Sam Melville-J. Jackson unit, 1976-1989 (Folder 2, Box 211)
    United Freedom Front
  - UN etc. bomb conspiracy, 1993 (Folder 3, Box 211)
    United Nations, FBI, Lincoln and Holland Tunnels, Bombing
  - United States Department of State: Soviet Influence Activities: A Report on Active Measures and Propaganda, 1986 - 1987", August 1987 (Folder 4, Box 211)
  - U.S.A. Court of Appeals - U.S.A. as Plaintiff vs. Truong Dinh Hung and Ronald Humphrey as Defendants, 1979 (Folder 5, Box 211)
    National Defense, Trials
  - "US Counter Intelligence Today", Francis J. McNamara (Nathan Hall Institute), 1985-1991 (Folder 6, Box 211)
  - US incidents, 1976-1980 (Folder 7, Box 211)
    Bombings, Domestic Terrorism
  - US Needs a Policy for Political Warfare, 1988 (Folder 8, Box 211)
    Reserve Officers Association [ROA] National Security Report
  - US personnel abroad, 1978-1982 (Folder 9, Box 211)
    Bombing, Diplomats, Terrorism
  - USSR role, 1976-1984 (Folder 10, Box 211)
    Gorbachev, KGB, Soviet Union, Terrorism, Yeltsin
  - Varelli, Frank, 1986-1988 (Folder 11, Box 211)
    FBI, Varelli vs. United States of America
  - "Veil: The Secret Wars of the CIA" by Bob Woodward (also information on CIA Director William J. Casey, 1980s (Folder 12, Box 211)
    Casey, CIA, Book Reviews, Woodward
  - Vernon Jordan, 1980-1981 (Folder 13, Box 211)
    Coleman, FBI, Shooting
  - Visas, 1980s (Folder 1, Box 212)
    Castro, Foreign Exchange, Paisley, PLO
  - Walkers, 1980s (Folder 2, Box 212)
    Barbara Joy Crowley Walker, John A. Walker Jr., Espionage
  - Walkers, 1980s (Folder 3, Box 212)
  - Warnke, Paul, 1977-1981 (Folder 4, Box 212)
    Arms Control, Carter, Detente, SALT, SALT II
  - The Washington Post - The Imperfect Spy, 1992 (Folder 5, Box 212)
    CIA, Espionage, Clair George
  - Wattenberg [Ben J.], 1977-1978 (Folder 6, Box 212)
    "Against All Enemies", CIA, Fiction
  - Webster, William H., 1985-1994 (Folder 7, Box 212)
    Carter, CIA, FBI, Iran-Contra, Presidential Appointments
  - Webster, William H., 1978-1987 (Folder 8, Box 212)
  - Webster, William H., 1978-1987 (Folder 9, Box 212)
  - Webster, William H.-speeches, 1983-1988 (Folder 10, Box 212)
    Domestic Security, Espionage, FBI, Freedom of Information Act, Organized Crime, Terrorism
  - Webster, William H.-speeches, 1985-1987 (Folder 11, Box 212)
    Counterintelligence, Domestic Security, FBI, Organized Crime, Terrorism
  - Webster, William H.-speeches, 1985-1987 (Folder 1, Box 213)
  - Webster, William H.-speeches, 1985-1987 (Folder 2, Box 213)
  - "We Must Defend America" - Daniel O. Graham, 1983 (Folder 3, Box 213)
    Soviet Union, Strategic Defense Initiative, Reagan
  - Whistle blowers, 1978-1985 (Folder 4, Box 213)
    Pentagon
  - Whitworth, Jerry Alfred, 1985-1986 (Folder 5, Box 213)
  - "White Paper", 1981-1990 (Folder 6, Box 213)
    Soviet/Communist Intervention in El Salvador
  - White, Amb. Robert and Pastor Robert, 1986 (Folder 7, Box 213)
    El Salvador, International Center for Development Policy
  - William P. Barr, 1991 (Folder 8, Box 213)
    Attorney General, Presidential Appointments
  - William J. Casey, 1981-1987 (Folder 9, Box 213)
    CIA, Newspaper Clippings, Office of Strategic Services
  - William J. Casey, 1981-1987 (Folder 10, Box 213)
  - Wilkinson, Frank, 1982 (Folder 1, Box 214)
    Communism, FBI, Political Subversion, Transcript of Trial
  - Wise, David-Thomas Ross, 1981 (Folder 2, Box 214)
    CIA, Fiction, "Spectrum"
  - Woolsey, R. James, 1993-1995 (Folder 3, Box 214)
    CIA, Resignation
  - Workers Viewpoint Organization (Greensboro): Communist Workers Party, 1979-1989 (Folder 4, Box 214)
    Communist Workers Party, Ku Klux Klan
  - WPAX, 1981 (Folder 5, Box 214)
    Radicals, Radio Station
  - Wright, Jim, 1987-1989 (Folder 6, Box 214)
    CIA, Contras, El Salvador, HR 561, Nicaragua, Sandanistas
  - Young, Andrew, 1976-1981 (Folder 7, Box 214)
    Congressional Records, Diplomat, United Nations
  - Younis, Fawaz, 1989 (Folder 8, Box 214)
    Beirut, CIA, FBI, Hijacking, Trial
  - Yurchenko [Vitaly]-[Edward L.] Howard, 1985-1993 (Folder 9, Box 214)
    CIA, Espionage, KGB
  - Zia-Pakistan [assassination], 1988-1989 (Folder 10, Box 214)
    Assassination, Mohammed Zia ul-Haq, Pakistan
- Series 3: Regalia, 1950s; (1 box)
  The third series, consisting of one box, contains regalia and various artifacts such as stamps, notecards, and notebooks used by McNamara. Items are loose within the box (no folders).
  - The Communist Conspiracy, 1950s; 1.
    Communism, Reverend Cletus Healy
  - House Un-American Activities Committee [Sign], 1950s; 2.
  - Notecards, 1950s; 3.
    Card Catalogue, Court Hearings, Trials
  - Notecards, 1950s; 4.
    McNamara, Personal Identification, Speeches
  - Rubber Stamps, 1950s; 5.
  - SACB- Board Member Identification Cards, 1950s; 6.
  - SACB- Employee Identification Cards, 1950s; 7.
  - Superior Dial Time Stamp, 1950s; 8.